https://www.marriage-family-counseling.com/privacy-policy.html

Marriage & Family Counseling
Now Offering Online Couples Counseling
Our Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines
the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use
www.marriage-family-counseling.com, as well as some of the steps we take
to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed
decision about sharing personal information with us.www.marriage-family-counseling.com
strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and
integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting
our online visitors' privacy on our website.Personal Informationwww.marriage-family-counseling.com
collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our
website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on
a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, emai laddress, company
name and telephone number.This information is collected if you
request information from us,and sign up to join our email list or request
some other service orinformation from us. The information collected is
internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website,
notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.Once
information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we
make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable
information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal
information received from any visitor will be used only for internal
purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.Use of Cookies and Web BeaconsWe
may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies
are identifiers that are transferred toyour computer's hard drive
through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser.
The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or
register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables
www.marriage-family-counseling.com to recall your specific information on
subsequent visits.You have the ability to accept or decline
cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline
cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features
of the site.A web beacon is a transparent image file used to
monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites.They
are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire
third-party services to monitor traffic.They may be used in association
with cookies to understandhow visitors interact with the pages and
content on the pages of a web site.We may serve third party
advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads
being served on our website to ascertain how many times you've seen
an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is
provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally
identify you with that information on our web site.Browsers can be
set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being
sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either
of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you
so choose.Children's Online Privacy Protection ActThis
website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the
age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online
Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use
personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.Non-Personal InformationIn
some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally
identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual
users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users'
movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our
userbase as a whole.
The information collected is used solely for
internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial
purposes.Release of InformationIf
www.marriage-family-counseling.com is sold, the information we
have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site
may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the
service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will
receive notice through our website of that change in control and
practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the
purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe
provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to
protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal
information through our website and would like that information deleted
from our records or would liketo update or correct that information,
please use our Contact Us page.Updates and Effective Datewww.marriage-family-counseling.com
reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a
material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site
that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new
privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so
that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf
you do not agree to www.marriage-family-counseling.com’s Privacy Policy
as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any
services offered by this site.Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.Thank you.
HomeCounselorsEugene Kayser LMFTGottman Method TherapistJennifer McCarron LMFTRobert Hunt LMFTClient ToolsAssessment ToolsSatisfaction SurveyQuizesTrauma & PTSD EvaluationForums & BlogsRelationship ForumCouples BlogCounseling and Therapy Horror Stories - Do You Have One? Share It Here…ArticlesSigns Of An Emotional AffairThe Good Marriage: What Makes Marriage Work and What Won’t!The Right Divorce Coach can help you to survive, and grow strongerGood Marriage Counseling and Family Therapy can put your life back together.Marriage Is Good For Your HealthLooking for a Marriage Counselor or
Family Therapist in the Philadelphia area?News & ResourcesMarriage/Family NewsResourcesBooks We LikeDivorce & Affair Counseling
If you would like to receive the Couples Guide Newsletter containing articles on relationships, please sign up below.
Submit Your Email To Get The Couples Guide
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to send me a newsletter.
Subscribe Here
Visit  The Relationship Forum  to get and give advice on your relationship issues.If you're struggling with your relationship, this is the place to talk about it!Our counselors will answer your questions.And you, our readers, can offer advice from your experience.
"You gave us counseling without making either one of us feel that you were taking sides. You always maintained your impartiality with us.
You encouraged Rita to be more assertive in stating what she wanted to get from your counseling sessions, as well as what she wanted to get from the relationship.
You taught both of us better communication between ourselves, which lead to an emotional comfort level between us that didn't exist before.
You took control of the direction of the session if things were not moving along.Thanks so muchfor helping us."
Rita and Mark
Return to Home Page.
SBI!
